The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Teng Eight\NTeng Family Core Member\NMiddle stage Nascent Soul
Ancestor,
we are willing to die for the Teng Family.
It's just that...
even Teng One was defeated by Wang Lin.
I'm afraid we cannot win this fight.
You just have to delay him for one incense stick of time.
After that,
I will kill Wang Lin myself.
We will obey your orders, Ancestor.
Wang Lin,
why don't you surrender already ?
go to hell !
Blazing Sky Nine Feathers !
Go !
That's the killer move of Teng Seven !?
So the rest of the Core Family Members
are here to deal with me ?
Very good.
Die...
This...
What kind of spell is this !?
Stay hidden,
don't go anywhere.
The Core Members are dead.
Everyone, return to the inner city !
The Ancestor will be able to kill him !
Hurry up !
He can't keep this up for long.
This city has been here for hundreds of years.
Running away ?
Teng Bo\NTeng Family 9th generation\NLate stage Core Formation
How can you tolerate an intruder !?
Besides, the Ancestor is still in the city,
there is nothing to fear.
We will act together to kill the enemy.
All Teng Family Members,
follow me in this bloody battle !
That's right !
The intruder
must be killed !
Teng Huayuan,
are you a coward ?
Hold on,
don't retreat !
The Ancestor will definitely come !
Kill him !
Attack together !
Teng Huayuan,
do you remember
how you slaughtered my Wang Family ?
Today
I will
pay you back a thousand times.
Go !
That's...
the souls of the Core Members ?
Teng Huayuan,
Here are the gifts I specially prepared for you,
why don't you come to have a look ?
Wang Lin...
Suppress evil, eliminate the Demons,
connect to the Gods.
Divine Sword !
Fall !
A Soul Formation artifact ?
I see,
you let your family die
to gain time for this attack ?
Let me see how long you can withstand
the Divine Sword given to me by the Envoy
with your Nascent Soul cultivation.
I killed you once before.
I can kill you again !
A heaven defying
Soul Formation artifact...
Truly amazing.
But in order to control it,
you had to put your Nascent Soul level Divine Sense inside it.
That is its weakness,
what a waste...
Come back here.
Teng Huayuan,
long time no see.
Wang Lin...
How does it feel ?
Does it hurt ?
When you killed my whole family,
my heart also hurt.
You killed my grandchild Teng Li
so I destroyed your whole family.
Your Wang Family
deserved to die.
Nonsense !
In the cultivation world, grudges should never involve mortals.
Teng Huayuan, you violated this rule
so I will have you watch with your own eyes
the demise of the Teng Family you raised during hundreds of years !
First, I will kill your heart.
Then I will kill your body.
And finally destroy your Soul !
Ancestor, run away !
Bo'er...
It doesn't matter if we win or lose.
As long as the Ancestor is alive,
the Teng Family will come back to life !
Junior begs you,
go !
It's time for you to die !
Futile resistance.
The Divine Sword cannot kill you.
However,
the stalling was not for the sword,
but for the Reverse Formation !
The Teng Family cannot die
and I cannot die either !
Reverse formation ?
Ancestor !
Sacrifice the living.
Sacrifice the family's bloodline.
Invoke heavenly power !
Ancestor, please...
Save me !
These 400 years
have been a huge gamble.
If I lose today
the Teng Family
will be destroyed forever !
He's crazy...
He's crazy !
Daddy !
Dad...
Nooo !
Bo'er,
don't blame me.
The Teng Family
will not lose !
I gathered everyone's cultivation in the city,
to destroy you, Wang Lin !
I will refine you for a thousand years
and have you pay for your crimes a hundredfold !
I think your lightning artifact is specialized
in destroying Divine Sense of the same level.
But today,
I have merged the cultivation of my whole family to the level of...
Soul Formation !
Without your lightning,
you are worthless.
You're pathetic.
If I can kill you,
then I will restore the Teng Family
to its golden age !
Get lost !
Die !
Futile resistance.
How long will you last ?
Accept your death !
Enough !
Is this...
poison ?
Remnants of the poison of a Soul Formation cultivator.
Although it will not kill a Nascent Soul cultivator,
it's enough to deal with the souls of low-level cultivators.
Destroy !
Wang Lin,
I will kill you !
It's time to end this !
Teng Huayuan,
die !
Wang Lin,
stop !
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.